infinitylist.com 2013-06-04

# InfinityList – Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains in general terms how Infinity List protects the privacy of your personal information. We are firmly committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of personal information and maintain electronic and procedural safeguards to protect personal information in our care.

#### What is personal information?

Personal information is information or an opinion, in any form (whether true or not) about an individual whose identity is apparent or can reasonably be ascertained from the information or opinion.

#### How do we collect personal information?

In general, we collect personal information that you submit voluntarily through Infinity List. We may request information about you when you create or edit your account or user profile, upload Content; when you enter competitions, register for promotions or when you request information. We may also collect information when we invite you to complete surveys or provide us with feedback. Additionally, we collect any information that you voluntarily enter, including personal information into any postings, comments, or forums within the Infinity List community.

#### What personal information do we collect?

Generally, the type of personal information we collect about you is the information that is needed to facilitate uploading your Content. For example, we may collect details such as your name, location, email address. We also collect information that is required for use in the business activities of Infinity List.

We are required by law to obtain your consent to the collection of sensitive information. We will assume that you have consented to the collection of all information which is provided to us for use in accordance with this Policy, unless you tell us otherwise.

#### How do we use personal information?

We may use and disclose your personal information for the purposes for which it was collected, or for a related or ancillary purpose such as any one or more of the following purposes:

  * Identification of fraud or error;
  * Regulatory reporting and compliance;
  * Payment of royalties;
  * Developing, improving and marketing our services;
  * Servicing our relationship with you by, among other things, providing updates on promotions and services we think may interest you;
  * Involving you in market research gauging customer satisfaction and seeking feedback regarding our relationship with you; and
  * Internal administration.

#### Feedback

If you provide feedback to us, we may use and disclose such feedback for any purpose, provided we do not associate such feedback with your personal information. We will collect any information contained in such feedback and will treat the personal information in it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You agree that any such comments and any email you we receive becomes our property. We may use feedback for marketing purposes or to add to or modify our Site without paying any royalties or other compensation to you.

#### Is the information disclosed to third parties?

We may disclose your personal information:

  * as permitted or required by law;
  * to various regulatory bodies and law enforcement officials and agencies to protect against fraud and for related security purposes.

Other than the above, we will not disclose your personal information without your consent unless disclosure is either necessary to prevent a threat to life or health, authorised or required by law, reasonably necessary to enforce the law or necessary to investigate a suspected unlawful activity.

#### Security of information

Infinity List has implemented appropriate physical, electronic and managerial security procedures in an endeavor to protect personal information from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction. Even though we have taken significant steps to protect your personal information, no company, including us, can fully eliminate security risks associated with personal information.  
Infinity List regularly reviews security and encryption technologies and will strive to protect information to the fullest extent possible.

#### Access and correction of personal information

Subject to the exceptions set out in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth), we invite you to access and correct any personal information we may hold on you. If we deny access, we will provide you with the reason for such denial. We may recover from you our reasonable costs of supplying you with access to this information.

#### Linked sites

Our website may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of any linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

#### Changes to our Policy

From time to time it may be necessary for us to review and revise this policy. We reserve the right to change our policy at any time, should this occur the amendment will be displayed on our website.
